let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Jeff Bezos is the founder of?",
    answer: "Amazon",
    options: ["Subway", "Tesla", "Amazon", "Apple"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Lemurs are native to which country?",
    answer: "Madagascar",
    options: ["Peru", "Madagascar", "Cuba", "India"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "First colour television come out in?",
    answer: "1928",
    options: ["1936", "1954", "1945", "1928"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The Australian Flag has how many colours?",
    answer: "3",
    options: ["2", "3", "5", "4"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What was Walt Disney afraid of?",
    answer: "Mice",
    options: ["Spiders", "Mice", "Dogs", "Cats"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Name of the smallest bone in human body?",
    answer: "Stapes",
    options: ["Mandible", "Maxilla", "Ulna", "Stapes"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a fruit?",
    answer: "Rhubarb",
    options: ["Rhubarb", "Tomatoes", "Avocados", "Walnut"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Where was the first example of paper money used?",
    answer: "China",
    options: ["Greece", "Turkey", "China", "England"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The fear of insects is known as what?",
    answer: "Entomophobia",
    options: ["Arachnophobia", "Entomophobia", "Ailurophobia", "Mysophobia"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How long did dinosaurs live on the earth?",
    answer: "150-200 million years",
    options: [
      "100-150 million years",
      "50-100 million years",
      "200+ million years",
      "150-200 million years",
    ],
  },
];
